[
  {
    "front": "<!--...-->",
    "back": "Defines a comment"
  },
  {
    "front": "<!DOCTYPE>",
    "back": "Defines the document type"
  },
  {
    "front": "<a>",
    "back": "Defines a hyperlink"
  },
  {
    "front": "<abbr>",
    "back": "Defines an abbreviation or an acronym"
  },
  {
    "front": "<acronym>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use <abbr> instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<address>",
    "back": "Defines contact information for the author/owner of a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<applet>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use <embed> or <object> instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<area>",
    "back": "Defines an area inside an image map"
  },
  {
    "front": "<article>",
    "back": "Defines an article"
  },
  {
    "front": "<aside>",
    "back": "Defines content aside from the page content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<audio>",
    "back": "Defines embedded sound content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<b>",
    "back": "Defines bold text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<base>",
    "back": "Specifies the base URL/target for all relative URLs in a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<basefont>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use CSS instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<bdi>",
    "back": "Isolates text that might be formatted in a different direction"
  },
  {
    "front": "<bdo>",
    "back": "Overrides the current text direction"
  },
  {
    "front": "<big>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use CSS instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<blockquote>",
    "back": "Defines a section that is quoted from another source"
  },
  {
    "front": "<body>",
    "back": "Defines the document's body"
  },
  {
    "front": "<br>",
    "back": "Defines a single line break"
  },
  {
    "front": "<button>",
    "back": "Defines a clickable button"
  },
  {
    "front": "<canvas>",
    "back": "Used to draw graphics, on the fly, via scripting (usually JavaScript)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<caption>",
    "back": "Defines a table caption"
  },
  {
    "front": "<center>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use CSS instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<cite>",
    "back": "Defines the title of a work"
  },
  {
    "front": "<code>",
    "back": "Defines a piece of computer code"
  },
  {
    "front": "<col>",
    "back": "Specifies column properties for each column within a <colgroup> element"
  },
  {
    "front": "<colgroup>",
    "back": "Specifies a group of one or more columns in a table for formatting"
  },
  {
    "front": "<data>",
    "back": "Adds a machine-readable translation of a given content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<datalist>",
    "back": "Specifies a list of pre-defined options for input controls"
  },
  {
    "front": "<dd>",
    "back": "Defines a description/value of a term in a description list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<del>",
    "back": "Defines text that has been deleted from a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<details>",
    "back": "Defines additional details that the user can view or hide"
  },
  {
    "front": "<dfn>",
    "back": "Specifies a term that is going to be defined within the content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<dialog>",
    "back": "Defines a dialog box or window"
  },
  {
    "front": "<dir>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use <ul> instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<div>",
    "back": "Defines a section in a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<dl>",
    "back": "Defines a description list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<dt>",
    "back": "Defines a term/name in a description list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<em>",
    "back": "Defines emphasized text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<embed>",
    "back": "Defines a container for an external application"
  },
  {
    "front": "<fieldset>",
    "back": "Groups related elements in a form"
  },
  {
    "front": "<figcaption>",
    "back": "Defines a caption for a <figure> element"
  },
  {
    "front": "<figure>",
    "back": "Specifies self-contained content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<font>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use CSS instead."
  },
  {
    "front": "<footer>",
    "back": "Defines a footer for a document or section"
  },
  {
    "front": "<form>",
    "back": "Defines an HTML form for user input"
  },
  {
    "front": "<frame>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5."
  },
  {
    "front": "<frameset>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5."
  },
  {
    "front": "<h1> to <h6>",
    "back": "Defines HTML headings"
  },
  {
    "front": "<head>",
    "back": "Contains metadata/information for the document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<header>",
    "back": "Defines a header for a document or section"
  },
  {
    "front": "<hgroup>",
    "back": "Defines a header and related content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<hr>",
    "back": "Defines a thematic change in the content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<html>",
    "back": "Defines the root of an HTML document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<i>",
    "back": "Defines a part of text in an alternate voice or mood"
  },
  {
    "front": "<iframe>",
    "back": "Defines an inline frame"
  },
  {
    "front": "<img>",
    "back": "Defines an image"
  },
  {
    "front": "<input>",
    "back": "Defines an input control"
  },
  {
    "front": "<ins>",
    "back": "Defines a text that has been inserted into a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<kbd>",
    "back": "Defines keyboard input"
  },
  {
    "front": "<label>",
    "back": "Defines a label for an <input> element"
  },
  {
    "front": "<legend>",
    "back": "Defines a caption for a <fieldset> element"
  },
  {
    "front": "<li>",
    "back": "Defines a list item"
  },
  {
    "front": "<link>",
    "back": "Defines the relationship between a document and an external resource (most used to link to style sheets)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<main>",
    "back": "Specifies the main content of a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<map>",
    "back": "Defines an image map"
  },
  {
    "front": "<mark>",
    "back": "Defines marked/highlighted text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<menu>",
    "back": "Defines an unordered list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<meta>",
    "back": "Defines metadata about an HTML document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<meter>",
    "back": "Defines a scalar measurement within a known range (a gauge)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<nav>",
    "back": "Defines navigation links"
  },
  {
    "front": "<noframes>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Defines an alternate content for users that do not support frames"
  },
  {
    "front": "<noscript>",
    "back": "Defines an alternate content for users that do not support client-side scripts"
  },
  {
    "front": "<object>",
    "back": "Defines a container for an external application"
  },
  {
    "front": "<ol>",
    "back": "Defines an ordered list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<optgroup>",
    "back": "Defines a group of related options in a drop-down list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<option>",
    "back": "Defines an option in a drop-down list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<output>",
    "back": "Defines the result of a calculation"
  },
  {
    "front": "<p>",
    "back": "Defines a paragraph"
  },
  {
    "front": "<param>",
    "back": "Defines a parameter for an object"
  },
  {
    "front": "<picture>",
    "back": "Defines a container for multiple image resources"
  },
  {
    "front": "<pre>",
    "back": "Defines preformatted text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<progress>",
    "back": "Represents the progress of a task"
  },
  {
    "front": "<q>",
    "back": "Defines a short quotation"
  },
  {
    "front": "<rp>",
    "back": "Defines what to show in browsers that do not support ruby annotations"
  },
  {
    "front": "<rt>",
    "back": "Defines an explanation/pronunciation of characters (for East Asian typography)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<ruby>",
    "back": "Defines a ruby annotation (for East Asian typography)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<s>",
    "back": "Defines text that is no longer correct"
  },
  {
    "front": "<samp>",
    "back": "Defines sample output from a computer program"
  },
  {
    "front": "<script>",
    "back": "Defines a client-side script"
  },
  {
    "front": "<search>",
    "back": "Defines a search section"
  },
  {
    "front": "<section>",
    "back": "Defines a section in a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<select>",
    "back": "Defines a drop-down list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<small>",
    "back": "Defines smaller text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<source>",
    "back": "Defines multiple media resources for media elements (<video> and <audio>)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<span>",
    "back": "Defines a section in a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<strong>",
    "back": "Defines important text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<style>",
    "back": "Defines style information for a document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<sub>",
    "back": "Defines subscripted text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<summary>",
    "back": "Defines a visible heading for a <details> element"
  },
  {
    "front": "<sup>",
    "back": "Defines superscripted text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<svg>",
    "back": "Defines a container for SVG graphics"
  },
  {
    "front": "<table>",
    "back": "Defines a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<tbody>",
    "back": "Groups the body content in a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<td>",
    "back": "Defines a cell in a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<template>",
    "back": "Defines a container for content that should be hidden when the page loads"
  },
  {
    "front": "<textarea>",
    "back": "Defines a multiline input control (text area)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<tfoot>",
    "back": "Groups the footer content in a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<th>",
    "back": "Defines a header cell in a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<thead>",
    "back": "Groups the header content in a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<time>",
    "back": "Defines a specific time (or datetime)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<title>",
    "back": "Defines a title for the document"
  },
  {
    "front": "<tr>",
    "back": "Defines a row in a table"
  },
  {
    "front": "<track>",
    "back": "Defines text tracks for media elements (<video> and <audio>)"
  },
  {
    "front": "<tt>",
    "back": "Not supported in HTML5. Use CSS instead. Defines teletype text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<u>",
    "back": "Defines some text that is unarticulated and styled differently from normal text"
  },
  {
    "front": "<ul>",
    "back": "Defines an unordered list"
  },
  {
    "front": "<var>",
    "back": "Defines a variable"
  },
  {
    "front": "<video>",
    "back": "Defines embedded video content"
  },
  {
    "front": "<wbr>",
    "back": "Defines a possible line-break"
  }
]
